Stanislav Rud

Junior Front-end Developer

Birthday: 31 July 1990

City: Kharkov

Email: rudstanislav1990@gmail.com

Site: My website
Skype: zevas_2140

LinkedIn: LinkedIn



Hello, Friend! If you are reading this, then I have already passed the first stage of selection[©]

I'm 30 years old, and I'm self-taught front-end developer. Last year I was learning front-end development. I passed some several free, pay courses, and learned all necessary basic knowledge related to front-end programming. I'm pretty sure that I will absolutely fill the junior position. But if you are looking for a trainee candidate don't hesitate me and text me.

I strictly understand what I need, and I hope to find a company that can help me with my ambitions to grow and learn.

I have small, commercial experience in developing websites, landing pages, I have HUGE desire to develop, improve and continue! Use my skills in real projects!

Now I work system administrator but I want to change my profession!

Skills:

- ✓ HTML5
- ✓ CSS3, SCSS
- ✓ JavaScript
- ✓ React
- ✓ Redux
- ✓ API, REST API
- ✓ ajax
- ✓ Bootsrap
- ✓ Gulp
- ✓ Adobe Photoshop, Figma
- ✓ Git

Work Experience:

(2018 – today) System Administrator, GROUP OF COMPANIES "FACTOR"

- ✓ Server management, workstations, routers, switches and existing network applications.
- ✓ Monitoring and daily system checks.
- ✓ Diagnostics and resolving various technical issues related to hardware and software.

- ✓ Support for all network systems LAN, WAN.
- ✓ Ensuring network security and integrity.
- ✓ Backup, data recovery in case of failures or other situations, system and data recovery.
- ✓ Update all possible servers to the current version.
- ✓ Implemented system inventory system (GLPI + Fusion inventory).
- ✓ Automated some services.
- ✓ Segmentation of the network.
- ✓ Made seamless WIFI in office.
- ✓ Aggregation network interfaces (result: speed has increased by about 30%)

(2015 – 2018) System Administrator, Chain of supermarkets «CHUDO»

- ✓ Server management, workstations, computers, laptops, printers, routers, switches and existing network applications.
- ✓ Monitoring and daily system checks.
- ✓ Diagnostics and resolving various technical issues related to hardware and software.
- ✓ Laying, construction, support of all network systems LAN, WAN.
- ✓ Ensuring security and integrity of the network.
- ✓ Backup, data recovery in case of failures or other situations, system and data recovery.
- ✓ Opened new branches, shops.
- ✓ Connecting and configuring commercial equipment.
- ✓ Remote user support.
- ✓ Moved all physical servers to virtual.
- ✓ Implemented a Zabbix monitoring system.
- ✓ Built from scratch AD + GP + DNS + DHCP.
- ✓ Implemented a corporate mail.

(Front-end Experience)

I made some landing pages, authorization (registration) forms, sliders, - but it some no commercial works.

Helped my friend for his business, made landing page for his website, modify his website, squid, form authorization, orders send to telegram and other.

Now learning to React (free lesson in YouTube)

Education:

KHAI - (2007 - 2011)

Bachelor – Engineer Constructor Aircrafts and Helicopters.

KHAI - (2011 - 2013)

Specialist – Aircraft Testing and Certification.

Additional Education:

Telesens Academy (2015)

QA Core (manual testing WEB, mobile, desktop, UI, checklist, test cases, bug-report)
NT School (2018)

Front-End developer (HTML5/CSS3/SCSS/Flexbox).

A-Level (2018 – 2019)

Full Stack (HTML5/CSS3/Flexbox/JS/Git).

Additional information:

I like RUM[©]. My hobbies are restoring my old car, picking mushrooms, cycling, kayaking In free time, I learn React, JS, and English.

I have an understanding and basic experience working with such assemblers as Gulp, WebPack WordPress, Opencart.

I'm Hard-worker, punctual, executive, initiative and responsible! I would like to join a friendly team of professionals!

Thank you for watch this! Have a nice day!